let questions1 = [
    {
        question: "Re-processing material to make another product is known as ?",
        option: [
            "Reduce",
            "Reuse",
            "Recycle",
            "All of the above",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is an example of reducing ?",
        option: [
            "bringing newspapers to a recycling center",
            "using plastic bags as small garbage bags.",
            "using less water when you shower.",
            "all of the above.",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "What does the three R's of recycling mean?",
        option: [            
            "Refuse Repurpose Recycle",
            "Reduce Reuse Recycle",
            "Reduce Reuse Rethink",
            "Reduce Refuse Recycle",
        ],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "To treat used things so they can be used again is known as ? ",
        option: [            
            "Reduce",
            "Reuse",
            "Recycle",
            "All of the above",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following can be recycled ? ",
        option: [
            "soda bottle",
            "plastic spoon",
            "paper plates",
            "zip lock bags",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question:
            "What does the term 'Reduce' means ? ",
        option: [
            "Use something over and over again.",
            "Use less of something, creating smaller amounts of waste",
            "Make something into something new.",
            "All of these",
        ],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "How many times glass can be recycled without alteration ? ",
        option: [
            "Once",
            "Twice",
            "5-10 times",
            "Continuously",
        ],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "What is the term used to describe objects that are being washed and used again?",
        option: [
            "Reduce",
            "Reuse",
            "Recycle",
            "Rethink",
        ],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question:
            "Which type of plastic is more friendly to the environment ?",
        option: [
            "PVC",
            "HDPE",
            "PS",
            "PET",
    ],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "Which type of plastic is more dangerous to the environment?",
        option: [
            "PVC",
            "HDPE",
            "PS",
            "PET",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "How much of our household waste could be recycled?",
        option: [
            "more than 50% of it",
            "less than 25% of it",
            "nearly all of it",
            "about 10% of it",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "What is the best way to deal with our waste?",
        option: [
            "throw it in the bin",
            "recycle it",
            "reduce it",
            "reuse it",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "The recycling label has ?",
        option: [
            "One arrow",
            "Two arrow",
            "Three arrow",
            "A tree",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "Which one of the following is a good example of reducing ?",
        option: [
            "Not using plastic bags when shopping",
            "Recycling plastic",
            "Giving plastic bottles a new use or purpose.",
            "None of these",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following items will NOT compost well?",
        option: [
            "leaves",
            "food, excluding bones and meat",
            "grass clippings",
            "plastic bags",
        ],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "Use an old car tire as a swing is an example of ?",
        option: [
            "Reduce",
            "Reuse",
            "Recycle",
            "Trash",
        ],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "Louis sells his dinosaurs at school. This act is : ",
        option: [
            "Reduce",
            "Reuse",
            "Recycle",
            "Recreate",
        ],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question: ".What can you do to help stop plastic pollution ?",
        option: [
            "Reuse Shopping Bags",
            "Use steel straws ",
            "Pick up plastic litter",
            "All of them",
        ],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "Mandy turns her plastic drink bottles to plant holders. Which of the 3Rs is she practising?",
        option: [
            "Reducing",
            "Reusing",
            "Recycling",
            "None of these",
        ],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "If you choose to take reusable bags to the grocery store instead of getting the plastic bags provided, which practice you are following ?",
        option: [
            "Reducing",
            "Reusing",
            "Recycling",
            "Repurpose",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "What is a benefit of recycling?",
        option: [
            "Less trash filling up landfills",
            "Fewer resources taken from Earth",
            "Less pollution",
            "All of these",
        ],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is most similar to the process of recycling?",
        option: [
            "Bringing a reusable shopping bag to the grocery store",
            "Turning off the water while you brush your teeth",
            "Telling mail-order companies to stop sending you catalogs",
            "Turning part of an old t-shirt into a patch for your jeans",
        ],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "What would most likely happen if there were no recycling?",
        option: [
            "The planet would run out of fossil fuels more slowly",
            "Landfills would fill up faster",
            "The price of oil would decrease",
            "Global climate change would end",
        ],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "Mike did not want to throw away his pickle jar. Instead he decided to use it again. This is an example of ?",
        option: [
            "Reducing",
            "Reusing",
            "Recycling",
            "Repurpose",
        ],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "How long does plastic remain in the environment ?",
        option: [
            "It remains 10 years.",
            "It remains 100 years.",
            "It remains 1000 years.",
            "It remains forever.",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
];
